MEIBELYN ARIAS

UI/UX DESIGNER

732-705-0051 Meibelynaarias@gmail.com Meibelynarias.myportfolio.com Linkedin- Meibelyn Arias New Brunswick. New Jersey

SKILLS

- Prototyping
- Wireframing
- User Testing
- Bilingual
- Competitve Analysis
- User Research
- Mockups
- Visual Design

TOOLS

- Figma
- Adobe XD
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- HTML/CSS/Javascript
- Invision
- Github

UI/ UX Designer specializing in visual design and front-end development. Previously experienced in customer service, problem-solving and collaborative teamwork. Skilled in Figma, Adobe XD, Adobe Illustrator, and Adobe Photoshop.

PROJECTS

Intensive project-based training program with a focus on UI Design, UX Design, Front-End Development. Course Topics included mobile app Design, Responsive web design, interaction design, and animations, creating style guides, design principles, and heuristics ect.

35, Native Ios and Android App, 08/2021-09/2021

Designed Native ios and android film photography app by conducting competitive analysis, user research, user testing, using Figma and photoshop

Barista, Responisve Web App, 07/2021-09/2021

Designed a Responsive web app by conducting competitive analysis, user research, user testing, using Figma and photoshop

EXPERIENCE

Customer Service Representative, Navient, WFH, February/2021-Present

 Assisted clients in scheduling covid -19 Vaccines, which enabled the New jersey department of health to meet state and nationwide vaccination goals

Recreation Assitant, Complete Care, Plainfield, NJ, February /2021 - July/2021

 Lead group activities and assisted in recreational therapy modalities which enable clients rehabilitation and completion of therapy goals

Barista, Starbucks, East Brunswick, NJ, July /2015 - 2018

 Collaborated effectively as part of a team which increased store flow and productivity

EDUCATION

Career Foundry, UI/ UX Design Certificate, June 2021-November 2020